So Elon Musk bought Twitter, and it seems to
be a pretty split decision on the populace of the
people that use Twitter on whether they're excited that
Elon bought it or they're not happy at all
and kind of worried about where he's going to
take the platform. Mr. Musk buying Twitter is an
interesting move, especially considering that he is a
top 10 most followed account on the platform
and actively using. Some of his tweets have
even shaken markets. But regardless of your opinions
of Mr. Musk, him buying Twitter obviously comes with
a certain purpose. The guy is the CEO of two
of the biggest companies in the world and is
also involved in a number of other things, and of
course, keeping up his celebrity and personal brand.
So any move he actively chooses to make
in regards to buying companies and whatnot, obviously
has to come with a deal of responsibility,
purpose, and drive. If you look collectively of
all the companies that Elon is the head of,
and just kind of what the general purposes
he's bringing behind them, pretty much all of them
have in common that they want to further the
human race and make the world a better place.
Clearly, since he has so much going
on in his time as a CEO,
multiple companies, obviously him buying Twitter, he
wants to try to bring that same
approach to the platform. As an avid Twitter user
myself, I use it every single day. I'm also
curious as to what installments and changes Elon wants
to make to this platform. So in this video,
I want to break down five things that I think
that Elon is going to bring to the platform to
positively change it and make Twitter a better
place for us all. Before jumping into number one,
go ahead and comment down below what your thoughts
are on Elon buying Twitter, if you're for it,
if you're against it, and why. And be sure
to subscribe to the channel for more videos like
this and leave a like if you enjoy it.
So the first major thing that Elon's kind
of talked about and presented to the table in
regards to buying Twitter is he wants to remove
all the bots from the platform. If you ever looked
in the comments under a post and see accounts
that just look like there's not a lot of action
going on their account when it comes to
following, they seem like they're created pretty recently,
almost maybe leaving kind of like a spammy or
scammy type of comment. Well, Elon wants to put
something in place that could take out this
for good on Twitter. Currently on the platform,
bots are thriving, being able to like,
retweet, comment, and just tweet out random things,
that might have been pre-coded in. And I think
the reason because of this is because Twitter is a
publicly traded company. And one of the reasons why
Elon wants to take it private is because if
you're a publicly traded company, you have
to worry about shareholders and their opinions and
what they think of Twitter and where it's going
in the direction of its success. Well, if you have
bots that are actively boosting engagement
on the platform, retweeting, liking, commenting,
pre-coded to tweet things out, well, it's going
to boost the engagement numbers as well as elevate
the active monthly user numbers that Twitter has. So if
you're a bot that's going to be doing a lot of
that, you're going to want to be able to
get that information out there. So when presenting those
to shareholders, it looks favorably on the
company. So Elon taking the company private,
this will give him the ability to leave shareholder
opinions out of the discussion and cleaning up all
the bots that are on the platform. This
will also reinforce Elon's idea of creating more user
authentication, verifying who certain people are when
they join Twitter, that it's an actual human
being on the account or a business or a new
content page that people want to run and who's really
attached to it. This is kind of similar
how Facebook has Facebook pages, but you have to
have an admin and a single account to be
a part of that Facebook page. And hopefully this user
authentication will incentivize the user and make it
a better place to really want to create their
own content and bring more to the table because
they don't have to worry about bots spamming their
posts or just when consuming content, bots trying to
scam people. The next thing that I think Elon's
trying to bring to the table when it comes to
this has been talked about a lot is pulling back
on censorship of the platform. I think there's
some concern initially with this move for some
people because maybe they don't want
certain people allowed on the Twitter platform,
to be able to have enough voice to talk
to their community. But Elon stated that his mission and
goal with pulling back on the censorship and free
speech is because he wants both the most radical
and polarized 10% on each side of the
political spectrum to be equally unhappy with this decision,
meaning that you're not going to be able to
be able to cater to every single person's opinions,
wants and needs, but he wants to be able
to provide the same service and platform for all
the users that are authenticated on the Twitter
platform, regardless of where they stand on the
political spectrum. Elon's mission and goal with
pulling back on censorship and free speech is
to provide the same service and platform for
all the users that are authenticated on the Twitter
platform, regardless of where they stand on
the political spectrum. And this could go
from beyond politics with any individual that maybe
you don't agree with, or you don't like
their platform, you just don't like them in
general as a person. And Elon wants to make
sure that every single individual person that's on
the platform that's authenticated can have a voice.
And if they have to be shut down, it's
really only for specific reasons that are set in place.
The next thing that I think Elon wants to add
to the table is being able to pay creators better.
I think the best way that Elon's going
to go about this is using the current transformation
from between web two to web three
and using cryptocurrencies to be able to
pay creators. You know, in the esports world,
there's this thing kind of called play to earn,
where, you know, you can play a
game and there's developing companies doing this,
where you can play games and earn cryptocurrency
as you're playing them, depending on how well you
do and the different types of content that
you make within the realm. Well, bringing this to
Twitter, you know, there might be a tweet to
earn policy where the more content you create and the
better engagement that it gets, the more you're going
to be able to tweet to earn certain currencies
that are allowed on the platform. And I'm sure
that this is going to have to do with cryptocurrency.
Another reason why I think Elon's going to
bring this to the table is it's almost essential
that really the only top accounts on Twitter are
able to monetize themselves. And a lot of that has
to go through their own marketing, their
own affiliate marketing strategies that they bring
to the table. There's not too much that Twitter
is able to provide them in regards to monetary
payment. It really is regarded on their audience.
If you look at the current creator economy outside
of Twitter, it prioritizes a lot of short
form video content. So that's TikTok, Facebook reels,
Instagram reels, even YouTube shorts and Snapchat reels.
So that's a lot of content that they're
going to be able to monetize. And a lot of
that has to do with their own affiliate marketing strategies.
So that's TikTok, Facebook reels, Instagram
reels, even YouTube shorts and Snapchat reels.
And a lot of that has to do
with their own affiliate marketing strategies. So that's
going to be a lot of content that they're going
to be able to monetize. But if you look at the
domain of kind of the power players in
there, it's really TikTok and Facebook Instagram reels.
And those platforms pay out creators based on
the amount of views and engagement that they get,
something that Twitter is kind of lacking
on, especially since it's not really prioritizing
short form video content. I think Elon might set
something up like this to be able to pay
creators similar to how those platforms pay, but it
might be in the web three space and it
might be more towards the written form Twitter
SEO approved content versus the short form content.
So I think that's a really good point. And I
think that's a really good point. And I think that's
a really good point. And I think that's a really
good point. And I think that's a really good point.
Maybe short form video content, but who knows
Elon might bring a short form video content
platform to the table for Twitter. I want to
go back to this constant theme of user authentication.
If you bring the user authentication
more heavily to Twitter, then, you know,
the company itself would be able to verify
who certain creators are and with their account,
how much engagement that they drive to the
platform, how much good content that they create
and being able to verify users, they'll be
able to make sure that the right person
gets their payment. And it's not just some bot collecting
checks and trying to scam people. The fourth thing
that I think Elon's going to bring to the
Twitter platform is an open source algorithm.
The benefit of adding an open source algorithm
to the Twitter platform is one, it'll provide
more transparency for creators and users on how
the Twitter algorithm is working from a
business stance. Since Elon's taking the company private,
this will allow the change of the open
source algorithm and it will reduce the maintenance
costs for the software. It'll increase the speed
and make it more flexible as well as increase
security. Before we get into the last thing that
I think Elon's going to add to the Twitter platform,
go ahead and comment down below if there's
anything that I haven't mentioned in this video
that you think Elon's going to bring to the
table in regards to just making the Twitter platform
better. Is he going to add anything that
you think will make the Twitter platform worse?
Let us know in the comments. So last but
not least, the final thing that I think Elon's
going to bring to the Twitter platform, he even
ran a poll of this on his Twitter account,
and that is the infamous decision to bring
an edit button to Twitter. I think the majority
of Twitter users, especially looking at the results of
that poll that Elon launched are in favor of
adding an edit button to the Twitter platform,
but the world still remains a little divided as
there's still some users that probably are against this
move. So what exactly would be the effects of
implementing this change? Well, on the surface
level, adding an edit button to Twitter seems
like it'd be a simple thing, but in the
reality, this might change the integrity of the platform
of having the original stated tweets up there. My
personal idea on this topic would be being able to
add the edit button into Twitter, but implementing
some sort of a blockchain technology that would
be able to backtrack what the original or
edited version of the Twitter platform would look like.
So I'm going to go ahead and get started with
the first thing that I think Elon's going to bring to
the Twitter platform, and that is the fact that
Elon's going to bring an edit button to Twitter.
For the first thing, I'm going to go ahead and
get started with the first thing that I think Elon's going
to bring to Twitter. So I'm going to go ahead
and get started with the first thing that I think Elon's
going to bring to Twitter. For the first thing
that I think Elon's going to bring to Twitter.
But just having a backlog of everything that
was originally added or deleted from the tweet,
that way you keep the integrity of
what was tweeted out on the platform,
and you can't just make a sudden change
to certain tweets for various reasons. This also
falls in line with the user authentication thing
that needs to be implemented into the platform.
And keeping the authenticity in the original tweet
by having that backlog will be able to
show people that, hey, maybe they just needed to
make a quick edit or what exactly was the
change that they needed to make. But the
current tweet is as it sits on the platform.
platform can be updated and changed as needed,
but there's still a backlog that people can check
and to keep that authenticity with all the users
in the community. So that's pretty much my thoughts
on the five things that I think that Elon's
going to bring to the platform that's going to
positively impact it. If you want to comment
down below anything of your comments on this topic,
and if you enjoyed the video, please give
a subscribe and a like to the video,
and we'll see you in the next one. Thanks.